onlineretailer.net 2014-12-23

# Privacy Policy

Reed Exhibitions – Privacy Policy  
This Privacy Policy sets out how Reed Exhibitions collects, stores, uses and discloses personal information.  This Privacy Policy may be updated from time-to-time.

**Collection Of Personal Data  
**The personal information collected and maintained by us will depend on our interaction with you and generally includes your name, contact details and, where you purchase a ticket to an event or exhibition directly from us, credit card or debit card information.  We may also collect details of our past exhibitions or events which you have attended, and details of your preferences or interests where you have provided such information to us. We may also collect and maintain your sensitive information, which could include information about your membership of any professional associations.   
For employment applications, we may collect your name, address, contact details, current and past employment information, and educational qualifications.  For contractors, we may collect your name, contact details, ABN, and bank account details for payment purposes.  Where it is possible, we collect your personal information directly from you in person, in writing, over the telephone, by facsimile, by email or through social media.  In some circumstances, we may also collect it from third parties such as through referees listed on your CV, and marketing organisations, including through the use of purchased lists.  

**Use Of Personal Data**  
The main purpose for collecting your personal information is to enable us to provide our services of conducting events and exhibitions.  We may use and disclose your personal information for this and other purposes, including conducting our business; communicating with you; informing you about products or services which we think may be of interest to you; marketing, improving, supporting and enhancing our services; and meeting our legal obligations.

**Disclosing & Sharing Of Data**  
We may disclose your personal information to others for the purposes specified in the section above.  This may include disclosure to our related companies; other companies or individuals who assist us in supplying our services or who perform functions on our behalf, such as support services, technology hosting and cloud service providers; where required or authorised by law to do so; and to anyone else to whom you authorise us to disclose it. We may also disclose your personal information (but not sensitive information) to others we have business arrangements with to enable them to offer their products and services to you. We will not use or disclose your sensitive information for any purpose, other than the purpose for which it was collected or a directly related secondary purpose, unless you otherwise consent. These recipients may be located in countries where Reed Exhibitions has offices (see the locations listed at: [http://www.reedexpo.com/en/about-us/Locations/    ](http://www.reedexpo.com/en/about-us/Locations/%20%20%20%20%0d)

**Disclosure Of Personal Information Outside of Australia**  
In the instance where personal information is disclosed to an external company operating in a foreign company, we will ensure that the information is protected by law or a contract which upholds Australia Privacy Principles. 

**Access and Correction Of Personal Data**  
If you would like to request access to, or correction of, your personal information we hold about you, please contact us on the details set later in this policy. We will provide you with access to the information we hold about you, including for the purpose of correcting or updating that information, unless there is an exception which applies under the Australian Privacy Principles. We may recover from you our reasonable costs of supplying you with access to this information.  However, we will not charge you for the making of the request or to correct or update your personal information.  
Your request to provide access to this information will be dealt with as soon as reasonably practicable. If we refuse to provide you with access to, or correct, the information, we will generally notify you of our reasons for refusal to the extent required and how you may complain about the refusal.

**Quality Of Personal Information**  
Before we use or disclose your personal information, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete, relevant, up-to-date, and is not misleading. If you believe the information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or out-of-date, contact us as stated above and we will endeavour to either correct the information in our systems, or if necessary, discuss alternative action.

**Direct Marketing**  
Our direct marketing consists of a range of communications channels. We communicate to our members using postal mail, telephone, email and SMS and will only send you any advertisement, marketing or promotional material or product information, if you have elected to receive such information. You can change your mind about your preferences in respect of direct marketing at any time by using the unsubscribe information on every such contact, by updating your user profile or account data or by contacting us directly. ****

**Storage and Security Of Information  
**We will take such steps as are reasonable in the circumstances to protect your information from risks such as misuse, interference and loss, and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. We hold your personal information in a combination of hard copy and electronic files.  We have systems and procedures in place to safeguard information, including the use of technical measures such as encrypted servers and maintaining physical security in order to prevent unauthorised access to records, documents and materials. We will take steps to destroy or de-identify your personal information where we no longer require it.

**How To Make A Privacy Complaint  
**If you are not satisfied with our response or if there is a potential breach of this Privacy Statement or the Australian Privacy Principles, you should contact us (02) 9422 2544 and request that your complaint be directed to the Privacy Officer. If you are unhappy with our response, you may apply to the Office of the Privacy Commissioner to have your complaint investigated. 

**Website Tracking & Cookies  
**We may collect information about your visit to our site through cookies to assist us to measure and improve our website. Examples of information that we collect include: day and time of your visit, whether you have visited our website previously, whether you used a search engine to find us and some geographical information about what country and state you are in. You can set your browser to reject cookies, or to notify you when you receive one in order to accept or reject such receipt in each instance.

**Collection Statement  
**Reed Elsevier Australia Pty Limited and its related bodies corporate (the Reed Group) acknowledges and respects your privacy. **** The information you provide is being collected by Reed Exhibitions Australia Pty Ltd for the purpose of processing your registration or inquiry. The provision of the information requested is voluntary.  However, if you do not provide the information requested, we may be unable to process your registration or enquiry. ****

Exhibitions will use the information to keep you informed about products, services, offers and upcoming events and to improve services to you. Exhibitions will also share information about you with other members of the Reed Group for these purposes. However, neither Exhibitions nor other members of the Reed Group will send you information about these products or services if you ask us not to.  
If you do not want to receive information about our other products, services, offers or events please call us or email us. Exhibitions will also provide information about you to the sponsors of and the exhibitors in the Exhibition for the purpose of providing you with direct marketing offers, which we think, may be of interest to you. If you do not consent to this disclosure of information about you by Exhibitions please call us or email us.  You have a right to access the information the Reed Group holds about you.  Please direct any queries you may have in relation to the use of information about you to the number below.

**Opting Out Of Marketing Communications**   
If you have a concern about your privacy or a query on how your personal information is handled by Reed Exhibitions, please contact us on the following details: (02) 9422 2544. We will respond to your query or complaint as soon as reasonably practicable.  If you are not satisfied with our response, you may also contact the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner.
